<story>
    <author>Jolly Proudfoot</author>
    <date>02/02/2017</date>
    
    <headline>Celebrating Innovation: Kieran Boyle Profile</headline>
    <subheading>A glimpse into the life of Sustainable Life Styles CEO. From hobbyist to head of multi-million pounds company, in just a breeze.</subheading>
    
    <article>
   	<p>The work of award-winning CEO Kieran Boyle is a benchmark for the furnishings industry. We sat over tea with the man himself and had a lovely chat about home decor, home-made furniture and living the dream.</p>
	<p>About 5 years ago, Kieran's connection to the world of furniture was limited to his side-interest in DIY home improvements. He had a full time job as a business analyst at a famous investment bank. His evenings and weekends were spent crafting and creating pieces of furniture for his new condo.</p>
	<p>'I loved creating, with my own hands. The pieces I made were all from recovered wood, recycled materials. I was obsessed with having environmental-friendly furnishings. I would go to flea markets and find bargains. I refurbished so many pieces. It was a great past time for me', says Kieran.</p>
	<p>Soon after, his passion started occupying more and more time. He quit his job and started selling his works. Kieran has a quirky vision on what home furnishing should look like. His pieces combined the antique look with new technologies and materials. People loved his works and he found himself buried in orders. That is when Sustainable Life Styles was founded.</p> 
	<p>'I gathered a few friends, fellow enthusiasts from a local workshop. We pooled our resources and skills together. We worked day and night, but we loved it. It was our calling. Since then, the company grew so much. We found more people who share our beliefs and we have built a great community. Our employees don't come to work. They come to create. We're all artistis here.'</p>
	<p>'Our customers look for unique, and different pieces. That is what we offer. Our creed. You won't find anything alike in any of the high-street chair retailers. We have furnishings already available at our showroom, but most often we create pieces, together with the customers.'</p> 
	<p>'They tell us about their needs, their lifestyle, the way they envision the space of their homes. Sometimes we create whole rooms, sometimes they're looking for that one piece to complete their homes. We help our customers with everything. From floors, to decor. We form relationships, and that is what our brand is about.'</p>
	<p>Kieran Boyle's company has been awarded this year with three wins in the 53rd Annual Cozy Furniture Awards. He says he is very proud, and shares this honour with all his fellow colleagues. 'The awards are displayed throughout the company grounds. There's one in the workshop, one in the design room and one in the coffee room. They belong to all of us. They'll give us the confidence needed to move forward with all our beautiful projects'.</p>
    </article>
</story>
