<story>
    <author>Pamphila Brandybuck</author>
    <date>31/01/2017</date>
    
    <headline>Apple iFurniture review is in!</headline>
    <subheading>Lots of hype, but is it worth it? We have looked at them, and we are here to give you an answer</subheading>
    
    <article>
   	<p>A buzz of excitement has taken over the news since Apple's presentation of the iFurniture, last week.</p>
	<p>But while enthusiasts can't stop gushing about how amazing and life-changing this new line of furniture is, critics are wondering if the products are really worth it.</p>
	<p>Of course, like anything Apple designs, the pieces of furniture are beautiful to look at, but are they also practical? And does the price tag match the utility of the items?</p>
	<p>We have inspected the iFurniture and we are here to provide you with our unbiased review!</p>
	
	<p>iDesk (£1500): a desk made of white chipboard and the Apple logo, made of glass. You can find cheaper, better quality desks at IKEA.</p>
	<p>iSwivel (£700): just like a regular swivel desk chair, but with the Apple logo on the back.</p>
	<p>iLamp (£350): a lamp available in three different colours (space gray, gold and rose gold), with an Apple logo shaped bulb. Replacement bulbs are available for a mere £150 per piece.</p>
	<p>iCouch (£1900): fabric couch, with two mini tables integrated in the armrests, purposed to hold your MacBook (not Pro, the MacBook Pro is too heavy!). The tables sport the beautiful Apple logo, which lights when you place your laptop on it -- though you won't see it.</p>
	<p>iTable (£3500): hardwood table, allegedly for 6 people but to be honest, it will only fit 4. The Apple logo will beautifully glow in the middle of the table.</p>
	<p>iChair (£450): just like a chair, but with the Apple logo on the back.</p>
	<p>iBed (£2000): a beautiful chipboard bed, with the Apple logo encrusted in the headboard. Mattress available separately for a meagre sum of £1100 - what a bargain!</p>
	<p>iWardrobe (£2200): a two-doors wardrobe, with hanging space. No shelves available, as they are so last-year technology. The wardrobe features full-length mirrors on the exterior and the Apple logo will light up in the mirrors, to hinder your gawking.</p>
	<p>There is its, folks. Now happy shopping!</p>
    </article>
</story>
